<div>
    <h3>Creating a Custom Plan</h3>

    <p>To run the Phase 2 tests, you must submit a set of EPID images created by a compatible RTPLAN.</p>

    <p>Often simply copying an RTPLAN from another institution does not work because of incompatibilities
        with machine
        name, beam energies, and tolerance table names. The Customize Plan feature
        addresses this.
    </p>

    <p>The steps are:</p>

    <p>Navigate to Administration --> Machines</p>

    <p>Select the machine from the list that you wish to make the plan for. If it does not exist, use Create new Machine
        to create
        it.
    </p>

    <p>Make sure that the list of beam energies that your machine supports is correct.</p>

    <p>Click the Customize Plan button</p>

    <p>The following screen shot shows an example for a machine named Foo.</p>

    <img src="CustomizePlanUI.png" style="margin:30px;" />

    <p>Fill in the fields:</p>

    <p>
        <h4>Patient ID:</h4>
        This will be filled with a default value but you may override it with something that
        will make it easy for you to
        track in your system.
    </p>

    <p>
        <h4>Patient Name:</h4>
        Similar to Patient ID
    </p>

    <p>
        <h4>Tolerance Table Name:</h4>
        Initially empty, this must be filled with a tolerance table that your system supports.
    </p>

    <p>
        <h4>Machine Name:</h4>
        The name that your planning system expects. Some planning systems have different values for machine
        ID and
        machine name.
    </p>

    <p>Click the Create button and the following will be shown:</p>

    <img src="CustomizePlanDownload.png" style="margin:30px;" />

    <p>Click Download to download a DICOM version of the RTPLAN.</p>

    <p>The RTPLAN may then be imported into your planning system.</p>

    <p>Note: The AQA keeps track of custom made plans, so it is not necessary to upload them later.</p>
</div>